leaflink.com 2017-07-12

# LeafLink - Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

_**Effective Date: January 8, 2016**_

This Privacy Policy of LeafLink, Inc. (" **LeafLink** ", " **we** ", " **us** ", " **our** ") applies to the operations of LeafLink that we offer through our web application (the " **Service** "). It provides the policies and procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing the information of each user of the Service (" **you** ", " **your** ", or the " **User** "). We recognize that you choose to use the Service and we consider your privacy and the security of your personal information to be very important.

Throughout this Privacy Policy, we make reference to your Personally Identifiable Information (" **PII** ") that we collect. This refers to information about you as an individual, such that your identity can be reasonably ascertained. For example, your name, telephone number and email address are PII.

By using the Service, you accept the practices set forth in this Privacy Policy. Please read it carefully before using the Service. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, you may not access or otherwise use the Service.

#### _**Information We Collect**_

We receive and store information you give us when you use the Service. For example, we collect information when you: provide information to sign up for an account with the Service; provide information in your Account Profile; login and operate your account within the Service; or communicate with us by email for any purpose. You can choose not to provide certain information, but you may not be able to use all of the Service features as a result. We also collect general, statistical, Non-Personally identifiable Information (" **Non-PII** ") including, but not limited to, technical information about your device, system and application software.

#### _**Setting Up An Account**_

Should you request an account with the Service (an " **Account** "), LeafLink requires that you submit the following information:

  * First and Last Name 
  * Email Address 
  * Mailing Address 
  * Phone Number

You must also create a password to when signing up for our Service. LeafLink requires the non-optional information listed above in order to create and maintain your account. When you create an account you will also need to provide information for your Company, retailer or producer and products associated with your company. The information gathered for company representation includes but is not limited to:

  * Company Name 
  * Company Address 
  * Company Website 
  * Company Number 
  * A List of Product Names and Details 
  * Photos of Products (optional)

#### _**How We Use Your Information**_

LeafLink will not publish any of your operational or profile data in any personally identifiable way. We DO NOT sell your PII to third parties or mass marketers. Unless you consent to the disclosure of your PII, only LeafLink and our affiliates, technical consultants, third-party administrators and other specifically permitted third-parties who enhance the functionality of the Service or who provide associated services who make our Service available to you through their individual websites or apps or who have loyalty programs covering multiple brands, have access to this information. For example, we may work with agents to analyze data, operate promotions, provide marketing assistance, and/or provide customer service. These agents may have access to select portions of PII needed to perform their functions, but they may not use it for other purposes.

We use the PII that you provide to us in order to operate the Service, improve our Service, and communicate with you. We may send periodic product updates as well as Service-Account updates that may include, but are not limited to, notices required by law and/or notices of a change in this Privacy Policy. If you provide us with your email address, we reserve the right to send you marketing and promotional emails. You may opt out of receiving such communications from the Service by following the instructions included with those emails. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional emails, such as emails about your account with LeafLink or our ongoing business relations. You may also send requests about contact preferences or changes to personal information, including requests to opt out of sharing personal information with third parties, to our contact information below. We use Non-PII (anonymized data) in the aggregate to compile data trends, and otherwise analyze the performance of our Service. Non-PII will also facilitate the provision of software updates, product support, and other services to you. This aggregate data will in no way personally identify you or any other users of the Service.

Unfortunately, notwithstanding any steps taken by us, it is not possible to guarantee the security and integrity of data transmitted over the Internet. Consequently, while we take reasonable steps to protect your personal information, we cannot and do not warrant the security or integrity of any information you transmit to us when registering for our Service or otherwise. All such transmission of information is at your own risk. Even though we are committed to having our Service comply with this Privacy Policy, you are also responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your password and your PII.

#### _**Disclosure of Your Information**_

We reserve the right to release account information and other PII: when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; at the request of any judicial, administrative or similar proceeding such as a subpoena; to investigate suspected fraud, harassment, physical threats, or other violations of any state or federal law, rule or regulation; to protect the rights, property, or safety of the Service, our users, or others; or to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements.

#### _**Links to Other Sites**_

The Service may provide links that direct you away from the Service to outside websites. To the extent that occurs, those third-party websites are not operated by us and are beyond our control. These websites may independently collect data, or solicit personal information. When visiting these websites, you are subject to their privacy policies, and we encourage you to read them as well as any terms of use or service. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other websites and we cannot guarantee the security of any of your PII collected there.

#### _**Business Practices and Transfers**_

As our business evolves and our practices change, we will continue to update this Privacy Policy. We may periodically notify users of changes in our policies and you should check our Service frequently for any changes. Your continued use of the Service is considered assent to any such changes.

Additionally, as our business continues to grow, we may acquire or sell a business. We reserve the right to transfer customer information in connection with such a transaction, but such information remains subject to the provisions of any pre-existing Privacy Policy. In the event that LeafLink or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information may be one of the transferred assets.

#### _**Minors**_

This Site is offered and available to users who 18 years of age or older and reside in the United States or any of its territories or possessions. By using this Site, you represent and warrant that you are of legal age to form a binding contract with LeafLink and meet all of the foregoing eligibility requirements. If you do not meet all of these requirements, you must not access or use the Site. We do not intentionally seek to sell anything to, influence, collect information from or otherwise address individuals 13 years of age and younger, nor do we knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 through the Service.

#### _**Contact Information**_

**LeafLink, Inc.**  
85 Broad Street, 17th floor  
New York, NY 10004

1001 Bannock Street  
Denver, CO 80204   
By email: [info@leaflink.com](mailto:info@leaflink.com)

© LeafLink, Inc. 2017. All rights reserved.
